<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecipeHomework</string>

    <string-array name="recipe_names">
        <item>Cake</item>
        <item>Ice-Cream</item>
        <item>Pancakes</item>
        <item>Sandwich</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_description">
        <item>Cake placeholder text. A cake is a thing that is baked and you eat and is sweet and stuff.
        There are several different types of cakes and this is one of them. Cakes are generally used for parties but you can eat them whenever.</item>
        <item>Ice-Cream is another sweet thing, but this one is fairly cold. It is often super expensive here in Van but they are generally really good.
        I want to get some ice cream now :(</item>
        <item>Pancakes are cakes that you make in a pan (maybe). Running out of stuff to write by this point but this is much more fun than just copying stuff.
        Alright enough about pancakes now.</item>
        <item>Sandwich is not in fact a mythological creature (witch) that controls sand, but rather a salty food thing that has things between two breads.
        Fore some inexplicable reason it invites many ridiculous debates as to what is and is not categorized as a sandwich</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_text">
        <item>Ingredients
1/2 cup unsalted butter softened to room temperature (113g)
½ cup canola oil* (120ml)
1 1/2 cup sugar 300g
4 eggs room temperature preferred
1 Tablespoon vanilla extract
3 cups all-purpose flour (390g)
1 Tablespoon baking powder
1/2 teaspoon salt
1 1/4 cup buttermilk room temperature preferred (300ml)
1 batch Chocolate Frosting

</item>
        <item>INGREDIENTS
4 large egg yolks
2/3 cup granulated sugar
1 1/2 cups whole milk
1 vanilla bean or 1 teaspoon vanilla extract
1 1/2 cups heavy cream
EQUIPMENT
Mixing bowls
Fine-mesh strainer
Whisk
Measuring cups and spoons
Medium saucepan
Spatula or wooden spoon
Instant-read thermometer
Ice cream machine
Wax paper</item>
        <item>The Dry Ingredients
Flour: Use all-purpose flour or whole wheat. A combination of the both is nice, too.
Sugar: We use granulated sugar, but you could experiment with brown sugar. Brown sugar will make the pancakes a little moister.
Baking Powder: Baking powder makes the pancakes so light and fluffy.
Salt: We like to use 3/4 teaspoon of coarse salt (or 1/2 teaspoon of fine salt). It balances the sugar nicely and brings out lots of flavor in the pancakes. If you are using salted butter, you may want to reduce this.</item>
        <item>2 x 200 - 250g/8oz-9oz pieces trimmed skirt of beef
4 garlic cloves, smashed and peeled
small bunch thyme

6 tbsp olive oil

1 oblong loaf sourdough bread
1 beefsteak tomato

, sliced
6 long leaves Cos lettuce
For the sauce
50g cocktail gherkin, finely chopped
1 heaped tbsp capers

, finely chopped
1 bunch flat-leaf parsley, leaves finely chopped
7 tbsp good-quality mayonnaise
splash Worcestershire sauce
4 shakes Tabasco sauce
1 small red onion

, finely chopped</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
